{"data":[{"question":"He _____ yet.","a":"don't finish","b":"didn't finish","c":"doesn't finish","d":"hasn't finished","answer":"4","explain":"- Negative: he\/she\/it + hasn't\/has not + p.p\n- Finish -> finished.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"I _____ to the gym for months.","a":"haven't be","b":"haven't been","c":"didn't be","d":"don't be","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the present perfect to say how long for an activity that happened in the past, and still continues now","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"Have you ever driven a car? No, I've never _____ one.","a":"drive","b":"driven","c":"drove","d":"driving","answer":"2","explain":"- Drive -> driven (irregular verb)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"What _____ doing lately?","a":"have you been","b":"you have been","c":"are you","d":"you are","answer":"1","explain":"- The question form: Wh...+ have\/has + been + S + V-ing...? (the present perfect continuous)\n- Be -> been.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"\"Where's Carol?\" - \" She _____ to church.\"","a":"has been","b":"is gone","c":"has gone","d":"is going","answer":"3","explain":"- Affirmative: He\/she\/it + has + p.p\n- Go -> gone.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"I have never been _____ Portugal.","a":"to","b":"at","c":"in","d":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Have\/has never been to somewhere (the present perfect)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"We _____ the tickets.","a":"are just buying","b":"just bought","c":"have just bought","d":"are already bought","answer":"3","explain":"- We use the present perfect for new happenings\n- Buy -> bought.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"How many times _____ to the USA?","a":"have you been","b":"you have been","c":"have you gone","d":"you have gone","answer":"1","explain":"- We use the present perfect continuous to say how many times for an completed actions ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"How many times _____ to the USA?","a":"have you been","b":"you have been","c":"have you gone","d":"you have gone","answer":"1","explain":"- We use the present perfect continuous to say how many times for an completed actions ","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"},{"question":"Who ________ written this article?","a":"have","b":"had","c":"has","d":"having","answer":"3","explain":"- The question form: Wh...+ have\/has + S + pat participle...?","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"5"}]}